{
    "subject": "resource/Andrew_Jackson_Montague",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Urbanna,_Virginia",
    "human_readable": "Andrew Jackson Montague died in Urbanna, Virginia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9856089949607849,
            "question": "Is Urbanna, Virginia associated with the death of Andrew Jackson Montague?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9624361395835876,
            "question": "Was Andrew Jackson Montague from Urbanna, Virginia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8880695104598999,
            "question": "Where did Andrew Jackson Montague die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.821826696395874,
            "question": "What was the name of the place where Andrew Jackson Montague died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.70769864320755,
            "question": "Can you tell me the location of Andrew Jackson Montague's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6526774168014526,
            "question": "To which place was Andrew Jackson Montague linked at the time of his death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.651029109954834,
            "question": "What city is connected to the death of Andrew Jackson Montague?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5191717147827148,
            "question": "In which state did Andrew Jackson Montague pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41511231660842896,
            "question": "Where did Andrew Jackson Montague meet his end?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3354742228984833,
            "question": "What is known about Andrew Jackson Montague's final resting place?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Andrew Jackson Montague died in Urbanna, Virginia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4075_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Andrew Jackson Montague meet his end?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4075_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which state did Andrew Jackson Montague pass away?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4075_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is connected to the death of Andrew Jackson Montague?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4075_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4075_22.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents confirm that Andrew Jackson Montague's location of death is indeed Urbanna, Virginia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe document states under the \"Location of death\" field that Andrew Jackson Montague died in Urbanna, VA. Therefore, the statement \"Andrew Jackson Montague died in Urbanna, Virginia\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}